Yes, we are live.
Yes, well, let's keep up the good work this week, shall we? Um, um...
Well, well, well...
A private exhibition.
Yes, sir.
Just now...
You see...
I don't want to lose to you with the funny face.
You can change your appearance any way you want, can't you?
Yes.
He's changing in so many ways.
I've changed a little too.
But unexpectedly...
I heard that...
I heard that moving these muscles in the face like this
It's really good.
What? It's good?
Yes, that's right.
It activates the brain as a whole.
Then let's all do it together.
Ready?
All right.
So...
Like this.
And like this.
I don't know about the photographers who take close-ups.
This is what I became a photographer to do.
I became a photographer to do this.
I think you're thinking a little bit.
I'm sure you're thinking, “Why did I become a photographer to do this?
Why do you want me to take better pictures of the scenery?
Thank you for always taking pictures of my funny faces.
And the funny thing about gyoza bread is that sometimes, when she's not in the mood to do something...
she's making funny faces.
I never get tired of it.
It's interesting when you watch it with this in mind, but... it's the rivals like Ebitu who explode.
And then the camera will show up on the big screen like this.
It's very interesting.
It's a very determined face, isn't it?
When he's making a good decision, of course he's making a good decision.
But on stage, you know, they're doing all kinds of things.
He stands out and looks like a dumpling bun.
But when Yori's face suddenly appears, it's like...
I don't know what it is, but she looks like Inoki.
And I, well, the people in the audience, well, they're just like, “Oh, wow!
I'm trying to hold back my laughter.
I mean, what great timing.
I'm so glad. I'm so glad.
That was awesome. That was... that was... that was...
I'm glad you laughed.
It's funny when he comes in unexpectedly with the cut.
I'm glad.
And they weren't trying to get laughs at all.
It's like they're not trying to get laughs at all.
The name of this week's Devil's Name is a bit long, but it's “Devil.” The dumpling buns that were made on the first day of the year.
I turned 24, but I couldn't make it here in June.
You mean you couldn't make it?
No? - No.
No.
No?
Well, well, well.
Well, well, well, well.
I can't help it.
Hey, hey, hey, maybe some other time.
Wow!
I'm just saying...
I mean, they were like 20 when they first came out.
I was like 20, 19...
I was just turning 20, so it's pretty much like what happens when you come of age.
That's right.
Wow.
That's for sure.
She's a full-grown woman, isn't she?
Yes, I am.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my.
Why Inoki?
That was a great moment, wasn't it?
It was so good!
It's like the beauty of dumpling buns.
Inoki's the best looking dumpling bun...
And it wasn't Inoki!
And it's not Inoki!
Well, well, well, well... So, let's talk about something more than that, shall we?
Let's go!
I don't know what I should do... I'm just about to say something about this corner.
You've been here for a long time, haven't you?
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
You can't see the pictures if you're watching the live broadcast.
I'm really sorry, but...
Of all the letters I've received this week, this is the one that I've read over and over again the longest.
And he sent me a picture.
There's a picture I saw.
Matsuro in Yamato City.
Thank you.
The title of the photo is...
There were a lot of railroad tracks.
There must have been a lot of railroad tracks.
He sent me these pictures.
This one.
But you know what?
In the Yokohama area...
There are a lot of train lines coming from here.
There are a lot of places like this.
But when I saw this picture
I thought, “Wait a minute.
The first thing I can think of is
From Yokohama station
There are a lot of train lines over there.
It's like this, right?
And from Yokohama Station to Keihin Tohoku Line
Towards Tsurumi and so on
There's a lot of Tokaido Line and so on.
I thought it must be one or the other.
Look at this picture carefully and you can see which one it is.
I'd like to know, wouldn't you?
That's for sure.
I wonder if there are many clues hidden in this picture.
First of all...
Here...
Over there...
It's going up.
This looks like a railroad track.
I think it's the Tsurumi Line.
The Tsurumi Line, I think.
I can only think of the Tsurumi Line in this area of Kanagawa Prefecture.
Tsurumi Line is the only line I can think of.
So I thought it must be near Tsurumi station.
No, wait, the Tsurumi line runs parallel to the JR line.
Where the Tsurumi line runs parallel to JR line, there are no buildings like this.
There should be a building on the other side of the street.
Anyway, I wondered if there were any clues here or there.
I was wondering if there's some kind of lettering or something.
I wondered if there was anything.
There's a clue on the building over there.
Can I show you this?
I think it's a railroad track.
Here...
Here's the building.
Here, put something on it.
It's only this one, right?
It says “something” on it.
But I'm having trouble reading it.
Various things.
I'm looking for that thing near the crane.
I looked on Google and stuff.
I also looked on Street View, but I couldn't find it, so I don't know where it is.
Mr. Matsuo, if you're watching this now, please let me know where it is.
Also, as a hint... this...
I don't know... some kind of... something... express...
Like a drugstore. Like a drugstore.
I think that's it.
I don't see anything like that in Tsurumi.
So it's not Tsurumi, which means it's not on the Tsurumi Line.
I wonder...
I see.
And if this is the JR Tsurumi Line and this is the Tsurumi Line...
If this is the JR Tsurumi Line, then there's a lot of tracks running parallel to each other like this.
It's really short.
There's only a short section just before Tsurumi station.
I'm not talking about there. I'm talking about where is this?
Matsuro!
Please... come here.
And finally... this apartment... it's unique.
It's a unique pattern.
I searched for it.
Photos like this...
But they didn't come up.
Where was it taken?
I mean, why did you send me these pictures?
I can't help but be curious.
I'm so curious, so curious.
Isn't it on the Keikyu line or something?
I wonder if it's different.
I see... I also have an image of different rails. This way. Ah... Is it different?
I see.
I have an image that the rails are different again, don't I?
That's right, that's right.
Is it different?
Yes, it is. So the tracks are already amazing. So, I can think of another place where there are so many, you know, in Tokyo, like Nippori and that area.
Wow.
There's also the Shinkansen and so on.
I see, I see.
There are so many train lines there, too, so they're all lined up side by side.
But that's all I can think of.
Where is it?
I don't see Matsuro-san.
I don't see him.
But if I show this picture to everyone, I'm sure there will be people who will say, “This is definitely the place.
Surely, surely, surely.
Kamoshika? An antelope?
Not antelope, not antelope, not antelope.
Haisha's name.
It's written “somethingbe.
Somehow?
Somehow Bekka.
Does anyone have a “something-besika” near their house?
Somehow, someway, someway, someway...
A building.
I wonder if there is.
You can tell by the width of the tracks on the Keikyu Line.
I wonder if there's a fat day.
There are a lot of people who want to see it, aren't there?
I wonder if they can see it.
I wonder if you can see this... If you paint with a type camera, it doesn't show this or any other unnecessary information.
There's no way to check.
I've also got one that says it's near Shin-Kawasaki Station.
May I have a word?
One moment.
What's the number?
This way.
Ladies and gentlemen...
You'll see.
Do you see it in this picture?
It's amazing if you can tell from this.
You're a detective.
And there's no car in the picture.
This is the place.
That's right.
Here's a deer.
It's a little hard to see.
It's amazing!
The research is 1435mm wide, and who knows what the width is? Diameter 9 is 1435 mm.
Someone can tell me how wide it is.
I have no idea.
I'll give you a hint... the railing of this building...
It's like a fence.
The fence has a unique pattern.
That's all I know.
Also, there's a drugstore called “Something Express”.
I'm not sure if it's a drugstore or something like that.
I'll be in by the end of the day, please.
I'm really curious about you, Master.
I'm wearing short slippers.
I'm wearing short-slippers and I'm going to sleep in 15 minutes.
I'm sure you'll send me lots of nice pictures, too.
Oh, I like the picture of Mr. Matsuo.
Thank you very much.
It's said you can see a plant that blooms only once in a hundred years.
You can see a plant that blooms only once every 100 years.
And there's Hibiya Park in Tokyo, right?
Near the Hachioji Temple.
There.
Blue Dragon Zeran... a cool name for a blue dragon.
Yes, “Zetsu” means “under,” like “under the dragon.
There's a plant like this.
What's this?
Maybe it's a flower.
Wow!
That's so cool!
It's so cool!
What's going on here? That's so cool! What's going on? It's going like this.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's getting better and better.
It's like a tree.
Amazing!
This happens once in a hundred years.
Once in a hundred years.
Wow!
It's been 100 years!
I heard that they are blooming in Yokohama too!
I just saw this...
I won't be able to see it again.
That's right.
It's not like that.
Can you stop with the realistic surprise?
No, you don't get it either.
We don't know.
100 years.
125 years.
Wow.
Daisuke Nakajima is 125 years old.
I wonder how he feels
Same as ever
I wonder if he's doing this with Shingo, I wonder how he's doing with Shingo, I wonder how he's doing with Shingo
I wonder if he's doing it here with that signal and scene
I'm over 10024 years old. Over 100 years old. But you know, I'd like to see the freshly made gold fish board as a grandmother, wouldn't you?
I'm sure I want to be a grandmother as soon as possible.
The longer I live, the more I want to be a grandmother. The longer I'm old, the more my grandchildren will adore me.
Come on, grandma, grandma, make a funny face!
I can see it in their eyes.
I can see it. I can see it.
With a funny face.
You make funny faces, grandma! Thanks again today!
I'm sure you're right.
Let's go to the creatures!
ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah
I'm sure you'll be able to find a way to get a good deal on it.
I'm sure you've heard a lot about Thailand this week, right?
As it happens, Gazelle also happened to send it to me!
What a surprise... Thai!
Thai language?
Luke Auto in Thai!
Hmm?
What?
Luke Auto?
Luke Auto.
It's kind of like that car factory in town.
Luke Auto?
Let's go to Luke Auto and get our car fixed.
Like Luke Auto Kawasaki.
He said if you bring it to him, he'll do it.
Sounds possible.
Luke's Auto is a little...
A creature?
It's a creature.
By the way...
There it is.
It looks like a crane.
It looks like a Tsurumi.
I'm pretty sure that's a Tsurumi ship, the one that's going up.
The Tsurumi Line is very old.
The bridge girder is a unique concrete structure.
It's definitely Tsurumi.
But there's no place like that in Tsurumi.
You mean somewhere in Tsurumi?
That's right... so it's definitely in Tsurumi.
Wait a minute...
hang in there Mr. Eiji.
But the Tsurumi Line was over there on that side of the tracks... ah... wait a minute... Eiji... hang in there...
But the Tsurumi Line, that thing on the tracks, there was the Tsurumi Line over there, wasn't there?
The Tsurumi Line comes over the top of the tracks, like this.
The Tsurumi Line goes over the tracks like this.
That's why you can see it over there.
So, if you can see it over here, it means that it goes from here to Tsurumi station.
That's the only place I can think of today.
I see.
I knew it.
But it's not there.
Oh well... hey, Luke Auto.
Luke Auto Kawasaki
Luke's Auto Kawasaki is expanding.
It's a creature, isn't it?
It's a living thing.
It's not a car.
Yes, it is.
I wonder what it is.
I don't know.
LUKU AUTO
LUKE QUOTE
I really can't imagine what it is.
Hey...
Thai is so... Thai is so...
Hey, Thai language!
But it has to be this one. It's a familiar creature.
What's that sound? I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I hope I get it at the end... the train tracks...
I don't know what it is.
But it's fun to imagine things like this, isn't it?
Wait a minute...
If you don't like the Tsurumi Line...
Luke Auto
Okay, yeah, Luke Auto, sure.
But Keikyu is probably supposed to be up there, that part of Tsurumi.
So it shouldn't exist there... with the tracks parallel to it.
Well no no no, we're already together on that one.
Come on, then. Luke Auto.
Okay, let's go to the doctor first.
Luke Auto, this way.
what is it?
A plant
Maybe it's like in the ground
Yes, it is.
It's a cross section.
It's like an old marriage.
Beet.
Beets.
Beets. Beets?
Beets? Dates?
beets? Beets?
What are you talking about?
They're kind of red. Like radishes?
Oh, yes. Like radishes. Is it a plant?
It's not a plant, is it? Not a plant.
Beets. Beets.
Heh. Is it?
Yes, yes. I was just thinking.
It's kind of like this.
So it's a plant.
Plants are living things too, right?
Of course they are.
I see. I was thinking outside the box.
It's okay, it's not the right answer.
I see.
I'm going to go ahead and say it's not the right answer.
So then...
Golden Freshly-Prepared Dumpling Buns...
Golden fresh dumpling buns.
Snake Snake...
White Snake.
A white one.
Albino.
Sort of like this.
Luke Auto
Seductive.
Like it's moving automatically.
It's like...
Luke Auto is...
Luke Auto is actually...
Luke Auto is actually a tadpole.
I heard it's actually about “tama-jaxi”!
I don't know what's going on here... but I've heard it's a very frustrating thing to hear about Thailand... in Japanese... of course... “Otamajaksi” in English... “Tat Pole” in Chinese... “Kedoh” in English... “Kedoh” in Japanese...
I don't know what's going on here... but I'm very disappointed in Thailand...
Spanish lenakwaho
French tetan
German kaukrapp eh, Kirk's sister was lost when she left.
Heber, I want an amphibian.
I don't want to be an amphibian, but no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
During summer vacation, elementary school kids make this kind of plant observation diary.
That's definitely more fun.
What's this?
It's amazing... they were just going on and on and on.
It represents the soil.
Well, well, well, well...
So that's how it is...
Just now...
You said, “Golden fresh dumplings and bread.
Give me your birthday present.
Don't play dumb with me.
Don't fuck with me, you bastard!
Did he say that?
What's the matter with you guys?
You're leaving? Like that.
Did I say that?
Actually, we have something for you!
Yes! Really? I thought you said you didn't have it, but are you sure?
Tatara!
Yay!
There's two.
Here you go.
It's pretty heavy.
What is it? There's a lot of these. May I?
Here you go.
First, this bag. Oh, it's so heavy!
What's this?
Artisan soy sauce.
Soy sauce?
Like a set of soy sauce.
Oh, my God!
You love soy sauce, don't you? Soy sauce.
I knew I wanted artisan soy sauce.
Can we open them one at a time? Yes, please.
Soy sauce, by the way.
Wow, there's a lot of stuff here.
Thank you for the debris charge.
Let me read them in order.
Yuki-san
DGP24
It's called HAPPY BAR.
Thank you.
Sorry.
Congratulations!
Oh.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I'm so chipper.
Oh, my God.
An assortment of soy sauce!
Wow! That's nice!
It's like each soy sauce is different.
Wow! Cool!
You mean they come out differently? Soy sauce.
First of all, it's soy sauce.
And Zard's sunset is late, but happy birthday to Po-chan and freshly made gyoza fan!
Happy birthday to a woman of the year, a woman of the year, 24 years old.
What's this?
3. Soy sauce dish.
Here's another soy sauce dish.
I'm the only one who serves it.
I'm the only one who puts out soy sauce.
You can set up a restaurant!
That's amazing.
You're right, you're right.
Thank you very much.
And, and, and, and...
And the other bag...
What is it? What is it?
It says “peppermill.
I see.
You cook.
That's cool.
Pepper. Pepper and salt.
It's a nutbar.
It's like this.
Wow, that's very stylish.
It's great. It goes with this.
This peppercorns and this Hirayama Salt.
You can really do it.
What's this?
I don't know.
There's one that's been carefully wrapped.
What is this?
Sesame oil.
Sesame oil!
Looks delicious!
What is the concept behind this one?
What would you like to use it for when you eat?
All of them!
Gyoza is wonderful!
Gyoza (dumplings) are wonderful!
I see.
Soy sauce with gyoza.
Yes, indeed.
Yay!
I'm so happy.
That's great!
Mr. Hamamin's golden DGP!
Happy booth day!
Happy birthday to Mr. Capricorn's golden ready-made dumpling buns!
Please help me prepare for my old age.
Thank you very much!
I'll enjoy my retirement.
You're right, there's no time like the present.
I'll enjoy it.
And Mr. Devilch, this is Gazelle.
Congratulations on your adoption!
And Mr. Tsukumoshiki, you've one-upped us.
I've one-upped you.
Thank you very much!
Congratulations to Mr. Kahi Kahi Hou for the gold DGP24 chai!
Congratulations to Mayu-san for the golden freshly made dumpling buns!
Thank you.
You are shining today!
Have a wonderful 24th birthday.
You're shining!
Thank you for a wonderful 24 years! You're shining! Thank you!
Have a wonderful 24th!
Thank you! Yay!
And Mr. Yudai?
Now I don't have to worry about food!
Happy birthday to Mr. Kim's freshly made dumpling bread!
Thank you very much!
Happy DGP to M. Nagaoka!
Thank you!
Happy DGP to Mr. White Sewing Kai!
Congratulations to Kahoriko on her 10th Anniversary Live!
Thank you!
I see.
I know.
I'll let you know in September.
On the 14th of September at J.com Hall Hachioji.
In celebration of Kahoriko's 10th anniversary.
Wow!
Just the two of you?
Look at that, Kahoriko!
It's been 10 years since lotus root and tendon.
It's just the two of us.
It's a two-person show.
I think it'll be interesting.
That's an unusual pattern, isn't it?
That's right.
This year is exactly 10 years since Riko and I
Riko and I have been with Eguchi for 10 years.
so please come and join us!
It's in Hachioji.
Thank you for the present!
I'll eat a lot of gyoza with it.
It's good.
It's his job.
All he does is think of presents for Ebichu.
He's very helpful.
He's free when there's no birthdays.
I'll be back next month.
Akira-san, the gold DGP is the cutest thing I've ever seen.
And Akira-san, we also got one who said that the gold DGP is the cutest!
Yay! Thank you!
We have already received many other comments and congratulations!
Thank you, everyone!
Now, this is for the backstage!
Yay! Thank you so much! You scared me.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, thank you.
Well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well...
I guess you didn't get it after all... about the train tracks?
I'll go to Tsurumi tomorrow.
I'm going to Tsurumi tomorrow.
I'll go check it out.
I can walk there.
I'll go, I'll go, I'll go, I'll go!
A little closer to Tsurumi Station.
That's right, the Tsurumi Line is right over there.
I can't think of anything else.
I see... that's right... between where the Tsurumi Line intersects with the Tsurumi Station.
I heard a whistling sound when it happened.
It was just a coincidence.
Well, that's about it.
I'll see you on the live feed.
It's across the street from Restaurant Burg.
Across from Restaurant Burg.
Restaurant Burg? Where's that?
I don't know.
Tell me about it.
It's a place called “Saito Shika”.
Saito Shika, apparently.
Saito deer.
Maybe it's not a deer.
I'm sure. I'm sure.
I didn't get a good look.
I vaguely recognized the deer.
Is this a place name?
Is it the name of a place called Tsurumigoro?
No?
Tsurumigoro?
No, it's not. Is it not? Tsurumigoro? No, sir. I read “Tsurumigoro” in the comments.
I wondered if there was such a place name.
No, no, no.
It's not near Tsurumigoro.
Maybe you live in Tsurumi?
Oh, you mean that?
Not near Tsurumigoro.
Maybe it's like a Tsurumi signal.
I don't know if it's like that.
Yes, yes, yes.
Wait a minute.
Oh, wait, the coordinates are out.
35 degrees, 35 degrees, 35 degrees, 35 degrees, 35 degrees, 35 degrees, 35 degrees, what do you do?
35 degrees, 30 apostrophes, that's 26 points, n, 139 degrees, 40 points, 34.e. If I look it up on the map, will it come up?
If I look it up on the map, will it show up?
Yes, that's right.
If you look it up on the map, you'll get the coordinates.
Why don't you tell me?
Where is this place?
The brown building in the back is Tsurumi University Hall.
Tsurumi Station is right in front of it
So we're near Tsurumi University Hall.
So you were right after all.
You're right.
There it is!
I'll go check it out tomorrow and take lots of pictures.
I'm curious.
Here... here are the coordinates.
Do this.
Yes, sir.
That's great.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Thank God we have social networking.
Thank God for social networking!
Thank God for the social networking society
Thank God we have a social networking society!
How did you find this?
I'm gonna copy that down a little bit.
Well done!
Well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well...
Oh, and that...
A picture.
I'm sorry to write this down, but...
I'm sorry to write this, but... this is the last one.
Nagano Prefecture
Beautiful
I went with a friend
I went there with a friend.
It was so cold
I was in the car in an instant.
Indeed.
The highlands of Nagano Prefecture
It's totally different.
It was so beautiful.
It was amazing!
The weather wasn't so great, so it was a little cloudy.
But the truth is, the scenery was more perky.
I was so happy. As a friend of Bullet's trip.
By the way, it's pretty close to where I was born, from here.
Oh, really?
Etherae's.
I'm right near Etherae and Swaco.
I see.
That's nice
I'm on the Nagano Shinkansen.
Yes
Oh, no. Nagano Express Nagano
Take it.
Oh.
Azusa.
Azusa... totally different.
Get on the Azusa.
Get on the Azusa from Shinjuku.
Ride Azusa from Shinjuku to Matsumoto.
I got off at Matsumoto and went to Shiojiri? I got off at Matsumoto and met my friend and he drove me there.
He was so cool and mature. Yes, it was my first time. It was like a trip for adults.
It was kind of a fun bullet train ride, and we ended up going to a ranch and some other places.
There is, you know, that neighborhood.
Really.
It was a full day.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Okay, well...